{
  "categories": [],
  "description": " Answer these questions about the music of the 1990's. ",
  "difficulty": -1,
  "questions": [{
    "answer": "Destiny's Child",
    "category": "1990's Music Trivia #2",
    "question": "What was the name of Beyoncé's girl group?"
  }, {
    "answer": "Candle in the Wind",
    "category": "1990's Music Trivia #2",
    "question": "What song about Marilyn Monroe did John Elton re-dedicate to Princess Diana?"
  }, {
    "answer": "The Bodyguard",
    "category": "1990's Music Trivia #2",
    "question": "What movie featured Whitney Houston's song \"I Will Always Love You\"?"
  }, {
    "answer": "Backstreet Boys",
    "category": "1990's Music Trivia #2",
    "question": "Who were the best-selling boyband of the 1990's?"
  }, {
    "answer": "Ginger Spice",
    "category": "1990's Music Trivia #2",
    "question": "What was Geri Halliwell also known as?"
  }, {
    "answer": "Meat Loaf",
    "category": "1990's Music Trivia #2",
    "question": "Who would do anything for love (but not that)?"
  }, {
    "answer": "Woodstock 1999",
    "category": "1990's Music Trivia #2",
    "question": "What anniversary rock festival in 1999 was not all about peace, love, and understanding?"
  }, {
    "answer": "Ironic",
    "category": "1990's Music Trivia #2",
    "question": "What word means \"ten thousand spoons, when all you need is a knife\"? (according to Alanis Morrissette)"
  }, {
    "answer": "Dr. Dre",
    "category": "1990's Music Trivia #2",
    "question": "Who discovered Snoop Dogg?"
  }, {
    "answer": "Sir Mix-a-Lot",
    "category": "1990's Music Trivia #2",
    "question": "Who liked big butts (and could not lie)?"
  }, {
    "answer": "Chumbawamba",
    "category": "1990's Music Trivia #2",
    "question": "What band got knocked down, but got up again?"
  }, {
    "answer": "Flavor Flav",
    "category": "1990's Music Trivia #2",
    "question": "What Public Enemy rapper wore a gigantic clock as a necklace?"
  }, {
    "answer": "Garth Brooks",
    "category": "1990's Music Trivia #2",
    "question": "Who was the best-selling country artist of the decade?"
  }, {
    "answer": "Take That",
    "category": "1990's Music Trivia #2",
    "question": "What band was Robbie Williams a member of?"
  }, {
    "answer": "Vogue",
    "category": "1990's Music Trivia #2",
    "question": "What song name-dropped Garbo, Monroe, Dietrich and DiMaggio?"
  }, {
    "answer": "Lauryn Hill",
    "category": "1990's Music Trivia #2",
    "question": "What singer was miseducated?"
  }, {
    "answer": "Philadelphia",
    "category": "1990's Music Trivia #2",
    "question": "What city did Boys II Men come from?"
  }, {
    "answer": "MC Hammer",
    "category": "1990's Music Trivia #2",
    "question": "Who toured around the world - from London to the Bay?"
  }, {
    "answer": "Nu Metal",
    "category": "1990's Music Trivia #2",
    "question": "What briefly-popular genre of music was exemplefied by KoЯn and Limp Bizkit?"
  }, {
    "answer": "Indigo Girls",
    "category": "1990's Music Trivia #2",
    "question": "What musical duo consisted of lesbian singers Amy Ray and Emily Saliers?"
  }, {
    "answer": "Gangsta's paradise",
    "category": "1990's Music Trivia #2",
    "question": "Which one of Coolio's song's was the best selling single of 1995?"
  }, {
    "answer": "Big Willie Style",
    "category": "1990's Music Trivia #2",
    "question": "What was the name of Will Smith's debut solo album"
  }, {
    "answer": "TLC",
    "category": "1990's Music Trivia #2",
    "question": "What group is comprised of Left Eye, T-Boz, and Chilli"
  }, {
    "answer": "Semi-Charmed life",
    "category": "1990's Music Trivia #2",
    "question": "What was Third Eye blind's first hit single"
  }],
  "quizLength": 20,
  "title": "1990's Music Trivia #2",
  "url": "http://www.jetpunk.com/quizzes/1990s-music-trivia-2"
}
